BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VII: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing
  - Code no.541338: American Standard Inc., Richmond Plant and International Molders and Allied Workers Union of North America, Local 164, 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Code no.550491: Chromium Corporation of America, Waterbury Plant and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, CIO, 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Code no.551560: North Electric Company of Galion, Ohio and International Union, Allied Industrial Workers of America, Local 481, 1964- 1970 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Code no.551809: Sperry Rand Corporation, Ford Instrument Division and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers-CLC, Local 425, 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Code no.551810: Sperry Rand Corporation, Ford Instrument Company Division and International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 471, 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Code no.560346: E.W. Bliss Company and International Molders and Allied Workers Union, Local 336, 1965-1970 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Code no.561496: Hamilton Cosco, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers Local 135, 1966- 1969 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Code no.561496: Hamilton Cosco, Inc. and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 1155, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Code no.561534: Seeburg Corporation, Cavalier Division and Allied Industrial Workers of America, Local 289, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Code no.561788: Reliance Electric and Engineering Company and International Association of Machinists, Local 439, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Code no.570283: Thiokol Chemical Corporation and United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipefitting Industry, Local 301, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Code no.570374: General Electric Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Code no.570379: General Electric Company, Euclid Lamp Plant and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1377, 1966- 1969 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Code no.570381: General Electric Company, Ballast Department and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 2076, 1966- 1969 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Code no.570411: Cornelius Company and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers Local 970, 1967- 1969 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Code no.570438: American Meter Company and International Union of Electrical Radio and Machine Workers-CLC, Local 144, 1967- 1969 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Code no.570646: Wood and Brooks Company and United Furniture Workers of America, Local 103, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Code no.570749: Scovil Manufacturing, Hamilton Beach Division and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 577, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Code no.580061: Teletype Corporation, Little Rock, Arkansas and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 2022, 1967- 1969 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Code no.580073: Fairbanks, Morse, Inc. and United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 234, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Series VIII: Industry Code #42, Wholesale Trade
  - Code no.560603: California Trucking Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers Locals 70,85,280,287,315, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Code no.560660: Mobil Oil Company and Independent Union of Socony Mobil Oil Company, Inc., 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Series IX: Industry Code #44, Retail Trade
  - Code no.560378: East Bay Motor Car Dealers, Inc. and East Bay Automotive Council, 1965-1968 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: East Bay Motor Car Dealers, Inc. and East Bay Automotive Council, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Agreement effective 06/01/1965 and expires on 06/01/1968. Covers 750 workers in East Bay, CA.
      Format: Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA).
  - Code no.560734: Robert Hall Clothes and Retail Store Employees' Union, Local 400, 1965-1968 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Robert Hall Clothes and Retail Store Employees' Union, Local 400, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 02/20/1965 and expires on 02/20/1968. Covers 100 workers in Washington, D.C.
  - Code no.560987: Akron-Canton Food Industry and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 427, 1965- 1968 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Akron-Canton Food Industry and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 427, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 09/12/1965 and expires on 09/07/1968. Covers 750 workers in Cuyahoga, OH; Lake, OH; Geauga, OH; Ashtabula, OH; Lorain, OH; Medina, OH; Erie, OH; Ashland, OH; Richland, OH; Huron, OH; Summit, OH; Stark, OH; Portage, OH.
  - Code no.561326: Dairy Employers' Labor Council and Milk Wagon Drivers, Dairy and Creamery Workers Local Union, Local 66, 1968- 1968 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Dairy Employers' Labor Council and Milk Wagon Drivers, Dairy and Creamery Workers Local Union, Local 66, 1966-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 04/01/1966 and expires on 03/31/1968. Covers 150 workers in Seattle, WA.
  - Code no.550415: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc. and Baker's Union, Local 19 of Cleveland, 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc. and Baker's Union, Local 19 of Cleveland, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 6, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 07/04/1964 and expires on 07/02/1967. Covers 275 workers in Cleveland, OH.
  - Code no.551146: Kroger Co. of Charleston, WV and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 347, 1964- 1967 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Kroger Co. of Charleston, WV and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 347, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 6, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 10/04/1964 and expires on 10/07/1967. Covers 800 workers in Charleston, WV.
  - Code no.551744: California Bakery Employers Association and American Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union, Local 24, 1964- 1967 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: California Bakery Employers Association and American Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union, Local 24, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 05/01/1964 and expires on 05/01/1967. Covers unknown number of workers workers in San Francisco, CA.
  - Code no.551964: Jewel Tea Company and United Retail Workers Union, 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Jewel Tea Company and United Retail Workers Union, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 07/19/1964 and expires on 07/15/1967. Covers 78 workers in Michigan City, IN.
    - Item 2: Jewel Tea Company and United Retail Workers Union, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 07/19/1964 and expires on 07/15/1967. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Michigan City, IN.
  - Code no.552255: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc. and Food Store Employees Union, Local 347, 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc. and Food Store Employees Union, Local 347, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 11/01/1964 and expires on 10/29/1967. Covers 475 workers in OH; WV; KY.
  - Code no.551357: Colonial Stores, Inc., Cincinnati Division and Cincinnati Warehouse Union 661, 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Colonial Stores, Inc., Cincinnati Division and Cincinnati Warehouse Union 661, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 04/04/1964 and expires on 04/02/1967. Covers 58 workers in Cincinnati, OH.
  - Code no.560326: Jewel Tea Company and Chicago Truck Drivers, Chauffeurs and Helpers Union of Chicago and Vicinity, 1964- 1967 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: Jewel Tea Company and Chicago Truck Drivers, Chauffeurs and Helpers Union of Chicago and Vicinity, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 01/01/1964 and expires on 03/31/1967. Covers 1000 workers in Chicago, IL.
  - Code no.560449: Best Markets, Inc. and Amalgamated Food Employees Union, Local 196, 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Best Markets, Inc. and Amalgamated Food Employees Union, Local 196, 1964-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 6, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 03/29/1964 and expires on 03/26/1966. Covers 80 workers in Philadelphia, PA.
  - Code no.561407: Long Island Gasoline Retailers Association, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers Local 917, 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Long Island Gasoline Retailers Association, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers Local 917, 1964-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 11/01/1964 and expires on 10/18/1966. Covers 65 workers in New York, NY.
  - Code no.550458: Employers in Pierce County, Washington and Retail Clerks International Association, Local 367, 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: Employers in Pierce County, Washington and Retail Clerks International Association, Local 367, 1964-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 6, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 10/01/1964 and expires on 10/01/1968. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Pierce, WA.
  - Code no.570215: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Retail Clerks International Association, Local 1636, 1966-1969 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Retail Clerks International Association, Local 1636, 1966-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 6, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 07/24/1966 and expires on 07/27/1969. Covers 570 workers in Tampa, FL.
  - Code no.570312: Retail Baking Industry in the Chicago Area and Retail Food and Drug Clerks Union, Locals 1550,1540,1504, 1966- 1969 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Retail Baking Industry in the Chicago Area and Retail Food and Drug Clerks Union, Locals 1550,1540,1504, 1966-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 6, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 10/20/1966 and expires on 10/12/1969. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Chicago, IL.
  - Code no.570572: Acme Markets, Inc. and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 692, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Acme Markets, Inc. and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 692, 1967-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 6, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 01/22/1967 and expires on 07/19/1969. Covers 600 workers in Baltimore, MD.
- Series X: Industry Code #45, Retail Trade
  - Code no.550159: Seattle Department Stores Association and Retail Clerks, Local 1207, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Series XI: Industry Code #48, Transportation and Warehousing
  - Code no.550755: Boston Shipping Organization, Inc. and International Longshoremen's Association Independent, Local 1066, 1958- 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Code no.560006: Deepwater Steamship Lines and Contracting Stevedores and International Longshoremen's Association, Locals 862-1624, 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Code no.560007: Deepwater Steamship Lines and Contracting Stevedores and International Longshoremen's Association, Locals 1736,1819, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Code no.570103: Clerk and Checkers Employers of Port of Charleston, SC and International Longshoremen's Association, Local 1771, 1964- 1968 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Code no.570265: Shenango Furnace Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Code no.551861: City Bus Company and Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 993, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Code no.561674: Eastern Massachusetts Street Railway Company and Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 1509, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Code no.580139: Town Taxi Company and Taxicab Drivers, Livery Chauffeurs, Ambulance Drivers and Helpers Union, Local 958, 1967- 1968 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Code no.550730: Meat Drivers of Chicago, Illinois and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 710, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Code no.552329: Murray's Fast Express and Murray's Fast Express and Independent Union 18, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Code no.560138: United Cab Association and Philadelphia Cab Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers Local 156, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Code no.560421: Akron Transportation Company and Transport Workers of America, Local 1, CIO, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Code no.550390: Murray Stevedoring Company, Inc. and International Longshoremen's Association, 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Code no.552209: Savannah Maritime Association and International Longshoremen's Association, Local 1414, 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Code no.561213: Connecticut Terminal Company, Inc. and International Longshoremen's Association, Local 1411, 1966-1971 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Code no.571015: Perini Corporation, Marine Division and National Maritime Division of America, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Code no.571157: Southwest Area Supplements and Riders and Road, City, Garage and Clerical Employees, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Code no.580138: Williams Auto Livery and Taxicab, Livery, and Ambulance Drivers and Helpers Union, Local 958, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Code no.590031: Neptune World-Wide Moving, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers Local 917, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Series XII: Industry Code #49, Transportation and Warehousing
  - Code no.552246: Gloucester Ice and Cold Storage Company and Gloucester Seafood Workers' Union, Local 2, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Code no.541123: Kroger Co. of Charleston, WV and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers Local 738, 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Code no.570300: United States Cold Storage Corporation, Chicago Plant and United Packinghouse Food and Allied Workers, Local 82, 1966- 1969 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Series XIII: Industry Code #51, Information
  - Code no.530230: Chicago Newspaper Publishers' Association and Chicago Mailers' Union No. 2, 1962-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Code no.580153: Collinwood Publishing Company and Cleveland Stereotypers' Union Local 22, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Code no.551891: South Jersey Television Cable Company and Communications Workers of America, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Code no.540834: General Telephone Company of Kentucky and Communications Workers of America, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Code no.550982: Knight Newspapers Inc. and Newspaper Guild of Detroit, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Code no.560383: Association of Motion Picture Producers Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers Local 300, 1965-1969 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Code no.560387: Association of Motion Picture Producers Inc. and Society of Motion Picture Art Directors, Local 876, 1965-1969 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Series XIV: Industry Code #52, Finance and Insurance
  - Code no.560106: Credit Bureau of Tacoma and Office Employees International Union, Local 23, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Series XV: Industry Code #54, Professional, Scientific, and Technical Services
  - Code no.570611: E.R. Squibb and Sons, Inc. and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-438, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Series XVI: Industry Code #56, Administrative and Support and Waste Management and Remediation Services
  - Code no.560303: Chicago and Suburban Ash and Scavenger Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers Local 731, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Code no.560173: Building Managers Association of Chicago and Chicago Window Washers' Union, Local 34, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Code no.561166: Building Owners and Managers Association of Seattle and Building Service Employees International Union, Local 6, 1966- 1969 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Code no.561443: Building and Managers Association of Seattle and Building Service Employees International Union, Local 6, 1966- 1969 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Series XVII: Code #62, Health Care and Social Assistance
  - Code no.570546: Kaiser Foundation Hospitals; Permanente Medical Group and California Nurses Association, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Code no.570466: Southern Pacific Memorial Hospitals, Inc. and Hospital and Institutional Workers' Union, Local 250, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Code no.570630: Hospital Service Plan of New Jersey and Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 32, 1966- 1968 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Code no.570630: Medical-Surgical Plan of New Jersey and Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 32, 1966- 1968 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Code no.580202: Southern Pacific Memorial Hospitals and Hospital and Institutional Workers' Union, Local 250, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Code no.580202: Southern Pacific Hospital Employees Association and Hospital and Institutional Workers' Union, Local 250, 1968- 1969 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Code no.580138: James Ambulance and Taxicab, Livery, and Ambulance Drivers and Helpers Union, Local 958, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Series XVIII: Code #71, Arts, Entertainment, and Recreation
  - Code no.552164: Metropolitan Museum of Art and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1503, 1965- 1967 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Code no.551712: Shubert Interests Operating Legitimate Theatres in New York City and Associated Musicians of Greater New York, Local 802, 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Series XIX: Code #72, Accommodation and Food Services
  - Code no.560900: Southern Oregon Hotel and Restaurant Association and Hotel and Restaurant Employee and Bartenders Local 329, 1965- 1967 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Code no.560422: Detroit Hotel Association and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 58, 1965-1969 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Code no.560423: Detroit Hotel Association and Building Service Employees International Union, Local 79, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Code no.570917: Greater Toledo Hotel and Motel Association and Building Service Employees' International Union, Local 3, 1967- 1969 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Code no.590298: Bell Brand Foods, Ltd. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers Local 683, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Series XX: Code #81, Other Services (except Public Administration)
  - Code no.560147: Parking Lots and Parking Garages, St. Louis and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers Local 618, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Code no.570098: Empire State Master Hairdressers, Inc. and Journeymen Barbers, Hairdressers, Cosmetologists and Proprietors' International Union of America, Local 17A, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Code no.552160: Barber Shops in St. Louis, Missouri and Journeymen Barbers, Hairdressers, Cosmetologists and Proprietors' International Union of America, Local 107, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Code no.552208: Professional Laundry Institute of Chicagoland and Automobile Mechanics' Local 701, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Code no.570337: Industrial Laundries Association of Kansas City and Laundry, Dry Cleaning and Dye House Workers' International Union, Local 238, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Code no.561702: Professional Laundry Institute of Chicagoland and Laundry, Dye House, Cleaning Drivers, Chauffeurs, Handlers, Solicitors and Salesmen, Local 712, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Code no.580138: Funeral Car Service and Taxicab, Livery, and Ambulance Drivers and Helpers Union, Local 958, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 62)